Snowed Inn Christmas is a comedy, romance, tv movie film directed by Gary Yates.
Jenna Hudson and Kevin Jenner are polar opposites working for
the same online publication in New York City.
With both having nowhere they want to be for Christmas, they
volunteer for a special writing assignment.
After a snowstorm forces their plane to land in none other than Santa Claus, Indiana, the two are placed in a Christmas
Wonderland and the focus of their story shifts to saving the historic town inn run by Carol and Christopher Winters.
As the two overcome their differences, they also
rediscover the magic of Christmas.
But with the inn's fate in jeopardy and the return of someone from Jenna's past, Carol
and Christopher lend a helping hand to bring Jenna and Kevin together.
Jenna Hudson, played by Bethany Joy Lenz.
Kevin Jenner, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Christopher Winters, played by John B. Lowe.
Carol Winters, played by Belinda Montgomery.
Women's Son, played by Jackson Blake.
Andrew, played by Jefferson Brown.
Snowed-Inn Christmas is a 2017 American-Canadian made-for-television romantic
comedy film directed by Gary Yates, from a screenplay by Carley Smale.
Starring Bethany Joy Lenz and Andrew Walker, it
premiered on 16 December 2017, on Lifetime.
The film explores themes of new york city,
indiana, usa, snowstorm, love, reporter.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.